=Love Lurking=
=الحب الكامن=
=Episode 4=
=الحلقة 4=
I will
أنا سوف
take her away now.
خذها بعيدا الآن.
Let Boss come to me.
دع الرئيس يأتي إلي.
I've already given you chances. You don't want it.
لقد أعطيتك فرصًا بالفعل، لكنك لا تريدها.
Get him!
احصل عليه!
Hold me tight
احتضني بقوة
and close your eyes.
وأغمض عينيك.
Why standing there?
لماذا تقف هناك؟
All go get him!
الجميع يذهبون للحصول عليه!
K,
ك,
you will regret this.
سوف تندم على هذا.
You're awake.
أنت مستيقظ.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I had a cleaning lady change your clothes.
لقد طلبت من عاملة النظافة أن تغير ملابسك.
I didn't tell them anything.
لم أخبرهم بأي شيء.
Can you untie this for me?
هل يمكنك أن تفك هذا من أجلي؟
I don't want to be like a prisoner.
لا أريد أن أكون مثل السجين.
You...
أنت...
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
This is a tracker.
هذا هو المتعقب.
You lied to me?
هل كذبت علي؟
Kun won't
لن يفعل أحد
give up easily.
استسلم بسهولة.
If you're in danger,
إذا كنت في خطر،
just press it.
فقط اضغط عليه.
I'll go to save you.
سأذهب لإنقاذك.
(A tracker?)
(متعقب؟)
(Then how can I escape?)
(فكيف يمكنني الهروب؟)
Forget about escaping.
انسى الهروب.
If you don't escape,
إذا لم تهرب،
I can keep you safe.
أستطيع أن أبقيك آمنًا.
If you run,
إذا ركضت،
you'll very likely die.
من المرجح جدًا أن تموت.
Understand?
يفهم؟
What if I'm willing to take my chances?
ماذا لو كنت على استعداد للمخاطرة؟
No one can escape from this island,
لا أحد يستطيع الهروب من هذه الجزيرة،
including myself.
بما فيهم أنا.
(It seems I need to rely on him to leave.)
(يبدو أنني بحاجة إلى الاعتماد عليه للمغادرة.)
Not this medicine.
ليس هذا الدواء.
Suddenly so nice to me...
فجأة أصبح لطيفًا جدًا معي...
What are you planning?
ماذا تخطط؟
You saved me.
لقد انقذتني.
I'm just repaying you.
أنا فقط أسدد لك .
That's enough.
هذا يكفي.
I haven't finished.
لم أنتهي بعد.
I don't like being touched.
أنا لا أحب أن يتم لمسي.
(He's like a brick wall.)
(إنه مثل جدار من الطوب.)
The wound on your head
الجرح في رأسك
can be fatal
يمكن أن تكون قاتلة
if it's not handled properly.
إذا لم يتم التعامل معه بشكل صحيح.
We are in the same boat now.
نحن في نفس القارب الآن.
You should at least trust me.
ينبغي عليك أن تثق بي على الأقل.
I won't run away anymore,
لن أهرب بعد الآن
nor will I reveal anything about you to anyone.
ولن أكشف عنك لأي أحد أي شيء.
But I hope
ولكنني آمل
you can protect me.
يمكنك حمايتي.
Don't you fear I'll betray you?
ألا تخاف من أن أخونك؟
I believe you are different from them.
أعتقد أنك مختلف عنهم.
♪I decide to wander♪
♪قررت أن أتجول♪
What's different?
ما المختلف؟
♪I smile to hide the sorrows♪
♪أبتسم لإخفاء الأحزان♪
♪How long must regrets linger♪
♪إلى متى يجب أن تستمر الندمات؟♪
You're so afraid of me.
أنت خائفة مني جدًا.
Yet you trust me?
ومع ذلك تثق بي؟
Well,
حسنًا،
I'm not afraid of you.
أنا لا أخاف منك.
Why?
لماذا؟
At least you haven't hurt me.
على الأقل أنت لم تؤذيني.
Alright, I will give you a chance.
حسنًا، سأعطيك فرصة.
Tonight we leave the island.
سنغادر الجزيرة الليلة.
I will hold Kun back for you.
سأمسك كون من أجلك.
You will help me?
هل ستساعدني؟
But if you fail to escape,
ولكن إذا فشلت في الهروب،
I'll definitely deal with you.
سأتعامل معك بالتأكيد.
Kun,
متى،
Boss will be back soon.
سوف يعود الرئيس قريبا.
Will we be doomed?
هل سنكون محكومين بالهلاك؟
The ledger is definitely with K.
الدفتر بالتأكيد مع K.
He saved that woman.
لقد أنقذ تلك المرأة.
That means he feels guilty.
وهذا يعني أنه يشعر بالذنب.
Go.
يذهب.
Find me a woman.
ابحث لي عن امرأة.
K.
ك.
What?
ماذا؟
You seem unhappy to see me.
يبدو أنك غير سعيد لرؤيتي.
Well,
حسنًا،
I was impulsive today.
لقد كنت متهورًا اليوم.
It's my fault.
إنه خطئي.
Dr. Gu,
الدكتور جو،
I apologize to you.
أعتذر لك.
What?
ماذا؟
Why be so petty?
لماذا تكون تافهاً هكذا؟
We are buddies.
نحن اصدقاء.
We share good things.
نحن نتشارك الأشياء الجيدة.
Today,
اليوم،
I've brought you a gift.
لقد أحضرت لك هدية.
The most beautiful woman in Tai City,
أجمل امرأة في مدينة تاي،
Wanida.
وانيدا.
Tonight,
الليلة،
have fun with K.
استمتع مع K.
K,
ك,
I want to learn to play billiards too.
أريد أن أتعلم لعب البلياردو أيضًا.
How would you like it?
كيف تريد ذلك؟
I want you to teach me personally.
أريدك أن تعلميني شخصيا.
Okay.
تمام.
Remember, we have plans tonight.
تذكر، لدينا خطط الليلة.
What plans?
ما هي الخطط؟
Make some room, okay?
افسح المجال لبعض الوقت، حسنًا؟
Don't get in our way.
لا تقف في طريقنا.
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Take this?
خذ هذا؟
Me?
أنا؟
K,
ك,
aren't you going to teach me?
هل لن تعلميني؟
Watch carefully.
شاهد بعناية.
Put your hand here.
ضع يدك هنا.
Relax your waist.
استرخي خصرك.
And your shoulders.
وأكتافك.
Then inhale
ثم استنشق
and exhale.
وازفر.
Strike.
يضرب.
Did you learn it?
هل تعلمته؟
Play by yourself.
العب بنفسك.
Your gift is too much.
هديتك كثيرة جدًا.
Keep it for yourself.
احتفظ بها لنفسك.
Boss.
رئيس.
Why did you come back early?
لماذا عدت مبكرا؟
Is she the woman you fancy?
هل هي المرأة التي تعجبك؟
You don't want any of the women given to you.
أنت لا تريد أن يتم إعطاؤك أيًا من النساء.
So you like this type.
إذن أنت تحب هذا النوع.
I think I've seen you somewhere.
أعتقد أنني رأيتك في مكان ما.
Sorry.
آسف.
I need to use the restroom.
أحتاج إلى استخدام الحمام.
(The person I have been looking for)
(الشخص الذي كنت أبحث عنه)
(turns out to be a drug dealer.)
(اتضح أنه تاجر مخدرات.)
(Why did he kill my mother?)
(لماذا قتل أمي؟)
I heard you two
لقد سمعتكما
had a big fight
كان لديه قتال كبير
over this woman.
على هذه المرأة.
Boss,
رئيس،
we didn't.
لم نفعل ذلك.
We're still buddies.
مازلنا أصدقاء.
K,
ك,
have a drink.
تناول مشروب.
Bro,
أخ،
drink this glass of wine
اشرب هذا الكأس من النبيذ
and forget about today.
وانسى اليوم.
Come on.
تعال.
I don't drink the wine handed over by others.
أنا لا أشرب الخمر الذي يقدمه لي الآخرون.
Did you handle the matter I entrusted to you?
هل قمت بمعالجة الأمر الذي أوكلته إليك؟
Yes.
نعم.
I'll kill you
سأقتلك
if you err again.
إذا أخطأت مرة أخرى.
Understood.
مفهومة.
(If I stay, he will recognize me sooner or later.)
(إذا بقيت، فسوف يتعرف علي عاجلاً أم آجلاً.)
Gu Nian,
قو نيان,
you don't need to go.
لا تحتاج للذهاب.
My men
رجالي
will take good care of K for you.
سوف أعتني بـ K جيدًا من أجلك.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Even if K was on guard,
حتى لو كان ك على الحراسة،
he wouldn't know the drug wasn't in the wine
لن يعرف أن المخدرات لم تكن في النبيذ
but on the rim of the glass.
ولكن على حافة الزجاج.
K,
ك,
compared to that woman, I'll make you happier.
مقارنة بتلك المرأة، سأجعلك أكثر سعادة.
I will take good care of you.
سأعتني بك جيدا.
♪What is secretly stirring♪
♪ما الذي يتحرك سرا♪
♪From your mouth, I find it hard to describe♪
♪من فمك، أجد صعوبة في وصفه♪
♪What praises can disappear in just a second♪
♪ما هي الثناءات التي يمكن أن تختفي في ثانية واحدة♪
♪Vanishing without a trace♪
♪الاختفاء دون أثر♪
♪Waving hands to break free from the splendid cage♪
♪تلويح الأيدي للتحرر من القفص الرائع♪
♪Words against the heart, a pain slashes through the sky♪
♪كلمات ضد القلب، ألم يشق السماء♪
♪Floating into the endless night sky, the wind fierce and strong♪
♪تطفو في سماء الليل اللامتناهية، والرياح شرسة وقوية♪
♪Who is reckless, continuing to lose control, with impunity♪
♪من هو المتهور، الذي يستمر في فقدان السيطرة، مع الإفلات من العقاب♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪
♪Cannot see who is pulling the strings behind♪
♪لا أستطيع أن أرى من يسحب الخيوط من الخلف♪
♪The wound still aches, and the memory is not yet over♪
♪الجرح لا يزال يؤلمني، والذكرى لم تنته بعد♪
♪There are two endings, whether you understand or not♪
♪هناك نهايتان، سواء فهمت أم لا♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪
♪Cannot see who is tracking from behind♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية من يتتبعني من الخلف♪
♪The heart still beats, total blood-red before my eyes♪
♪لا يزال القلب ينبض، أحمر اللون كالدم أمام عيني♪
♪Only one ending remains, whether it helps or not♪
♪تبقى نهاية واحدة فقط، سواء كانت مفيدة أم لا♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪